Register of the Committee for a Community of Democracies--USA records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Name lists and individual file, 1985-1991 (Box 18-20)
  - Individual files
    - Aldred, Ken (United Kingdom), 1985-1990 (Folder 18: 22)
    - Aloni, Shulamit (Israel), 1985-1987 (Folder 18: 23)
    - Aranda, Theodore (Belize), 1985-1986 (Folder 18: 24)
    - Arias Sanchez, Oscar (Costa Rica), 1988 (Folder 18: 25)
    - Ayala, Carlos (Venezuela), 1986-1987 (Folder 18: 26)
    - Balle, Francis (France), 1985-1989 (Folder 18: 27)
    - Bashiruddin, Ahmed (India), 1985 (Folder 18: 28)
    - Baume, Peter (Australia), 1987 (Folder 18: 29)
    - Bazar, Beatrice (Canada), 1985-1987 (Folder 18: 30)
    - Brecher, Irving (Canada), 1985-1986 (Folder 18: 31)
    - Bruin-Celli, Mario Tulio (Ecuador), 1987-1989 (Folder 18: 32)
    - Calderon, Ricardo Arias (Panama), 1985 (Folder 18: 33)
    - Carlton, James (Australia), 1987-1989 (Folder 18: 34)
    - Casanova, Tomas Puig (Chile), 1987 (Folder 18: 35)
    - Cerdas-Cruz, Rodolfo (Costa Rica), 1985-1987 (Folder 18: 36)
    - Chaney, Fred (Australia), 1985-1986 (Folder 18: 37)
    - Cohen, Armande (United Kingdom), 1986 (Folder 18: 38)
    - Coleman, Peter (Australia), 1985-1989 (Folder 18: 39)
    - Corterier, Peter (Germany), 1985-1987 (Folder 18: 40)
    - De Martini, Maria Rosa Segura (Argentina), undated (Folder 18: 41)
    - Deshpande, Arvind A. (India), 1987-1990 (Folder 19: 1)
    - Destremau, Bernard (France), 1986 (Folder 19: 2)
    - Donnelly, Dan K. (Canada), 1989 (Folder 19: 3)
    - Doyle, Fabio (Brazil), 1986-1987 (Folder 19: 4)
    - Eagleburger, Lawrence S., 1989 (Folder 19: 5)
    - Ehrnrooth, Georg C. (Finland), undated (Folder 19: 6)
    - Groenveld, K. (Netherlands), 1987 (Folder 19: 7)
    - Haagerup, Niels (Denmark), 1985 (Folder 19: 8)
    - Hermet, Guy (France), 1987-1988 (Folder 19: 9)
    - Jaguaribe, Helio (Brazil), 1987 (Folder 19: 10)
    - Kakizawa, Koji, 1989-1990 (Folder 19: 11)
    - Kaufman, Edy (Israel), 1987-1989 (Folder 19: 12)
    - Klebes, Heiner (France), 1989-1991 (Folder 19: 13)
    - Kosaka, Masataka (Japan), 1986-1988 (Folder 19: 14)
    - Lee, Young Ho (Korea), 1987-1988 (Folder 19: 15)
    - Legde, Angelika, 1987 (Folder 19: 16)
    - Leprette, Jacques (France), 1986-1988 (Folder 19: 17)
    - Lessing, H. W. (United Kingdom), 1985-1986 (Folder 19: 18)
    - Levy, Sam (Portugal), undated (Folder 19: 19)
    - Lightbourne, Dorothy C. (Jamaica), 1985-1986 (Folder 19: 20)
    - Mogensen, Ebbe (Denmark), 1985 (Folder 19: 21)
    - Monsod, Christian (Philippines), 1987-1989 (Folder 19: 22)
    - Mulimba, L. (Zambia), 1987 (Folder 19: 23)
    - Naka, Akira (Japan), 1985 (Folder 19: 24)
    - Nakasone, Yasuhiro (Japan), 1988 (Folder 19: 25)
    - Neckles, Donville C. (Grenada), 1986 (Folder 19: 26)
    - Nostrand, Howard L., 1990 (Folder 19: 27)
    - Nzouankeu, Jacques Mariel (Senegal), 1987-1991 (Folder 19: 28)
    - Obi-Nakamura, Toshio (Japan), 1987-1988 (Folder 19: 29)
    - Otero L., Miguel (Chile), 1989 (Folder 19: 30)
    - Poddar, S. (India), 1985 (Folder 19: 31)
    - Poveda Q., Jorge (Costa Rica), 1986-1987 (Folder 19: 32)
    - Reid, John M. (Canada), 1986-1987 (Folder 19: 33)
    - Revel, Jean-Francois (France), 1988-1989 (Folder 19: 34)
    - Rosenstiel, Francis (France), 1987 (Folder 19: 35)
    - Savidor, Menahem (Israel), 1985 (Folder 19: 36)
    - Samper, Ernesto (Columbia), 1985-1989 (Folder 19: 37)
    - Sethi, J. D. (India), 1985-1987 (Folder 19: 38)
    - Sharma, Harish (Fiji), 1987 (Folder 19: 39)
    - Shrestha, Gambhir Man (Nepal), 1986 (Folder 19: 40)
    - Slack, Timothy W. (England), 1987 (Folder 19: 41)
    - Toledo, Carolina (Bolivia), 1985-1988 (Folder 19: 42)
    - Uhrdin, Lars (Sweden), 1985-1989 (Folder 20: 1)
    - Van de Velde, Flor (Belgium), 1985 (Folder 20: 2)
    - Voorhoeve, Joris J. C. (Netherlands), 1985 (Folder 20: 3)
    - Walter, Harold (Mauritius), 1985-1986 (Folder 20: 4)
    - Wert, Jose Ignacio (Spain), 1986 (Folder 20: 5)
    - Wheeldon, John (Australia), 1985-1989 (Folder 20: 6)
    - Wickham, John (Barbados), 1986-1989 (Folder 20: 7)
    - Wilkinson, Paul (United Kingdom), 1986 (Folder 20: 8)
    - Younger, A. E. (United Kingdom), 1985-1988 (Folder 20: 9)
    - Zamir, Itzhak (Israel), 1987 (Folder 20: 10)
- Sound recordings, 1988 (Box 20)
  Includes speeches by Gerald Ford and Jimmy Carter given at the All-Democracies Conference in 1988.
  - Speakers at All-Democracies Conference, Michigan League Dinner, 1988 December 5 (Folder 20: 11)
    One compact sound cassette
  - Speeches of Gerald Ford and Jimmy Carter, 1988 December 5 (Folder 20: 12)